总共37分钟!
And time. 37 minutes!
我们从公寓出发坐地铁
We got from the apartment to the subway
到糕点学校的新纪录
To the pastry school in record time.
我想说我没穿胸罩
I mean, I'm not wearing a bra
然后丁字裤也可能穿反了
And my thong may be on backwards.
丁字裤怎么穿都可以的
There's no wrong way to wear a thong,
只要不会觉得穿着不舒服
As long as it's uncomfortable.
还有 胸罩对你而言就是个装饰
And with you, the bra's just for decoration.
我就得穿了 为此我会拿到一张票
I have to wear one 'cause you get a ticket
因为我没用胸把孩子们都挤到一个座位上
for not putting the kids in a car seat.
同学们 一会教室见
See you in class, guys.
我得先跟我老婆道别
I gotta say good-bye to my wife.
你真以为我要亲你?
Did you think I was gonna kiss you?
对啊 我是你老婆 你是我老公
Yes. I'm the wife, you're the husband,
有一天被我发现你穿着我的衣服
Who I caught wearing my clothes one day,
但我什么都没说
But I don't say anything about it.
各位早上好
Morning, guys.
Bebe 早啊
Oh, hi, Bebe.
看到我吓一跳 对吧?
Surprised to see me, right?
大家都以为我活不过漫漫长夜
Everyone always thinks I'm not gonna make it
但我活生生地出现了
Through the night, but here I am,
连我自己都觉得意外
Even surprised myself.
和一个随时会死翘董事的人
What's it like working in an office
在一起工作 有啥感觉?
with someone who's about to snap like a breadstick?
不如你想象中有趣
Not as much fun as you'd think.
但是Bebe人很好 而且在这里工作
But Bebe's sweet, and working here
能让你有钱念完糕点学校
is putting you through pastry school.
- 好吧 拜拜  - 拜
- Okay, bye.  - Bye.
- 我要离婚  - 我已提交申请了
- I want a divorce.  - I already filed.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 兜来兜去
时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 西皮JO xingzhenhang 初见
校对: 桃茜茜
对了 老婆 我要5块钱
Hey, wife, I need $5
赔偿昨天被我弄坏的抹刀
to pay for a spatula I broke yesterday.
当时我正幻想着厨神戈登•拉姆齐
I was having a Gordon Ramsay moment.
顺便说一下 我要和他嘿咻
I'd have sex with him, by the way.
为啥? 他会冲你大声嚷嚷
Why? He'd just be yelling at you
然后说你做的方式不对
and telling you you're doing it wrong.
是啊 做爱不对
Yeah, sex.
拿着 在我钱包里
Take it. It's in my purse.
哎 Bebe 你服的那些药
Yo, Bebe, you got any extra pills
还有没有剩余的啊?
you're not taking?
没有 我全吃了
No, I'm taking them all.
天啊 不
Oh, my god, no.
什么 我想要个一两片
What? I just wanted one. Or two.
让我缓一缓情绪
Just to take the edge off.
我三点还有个打发奶油的考试
I have a whipped cream final at 3:00.
不是 这有个讣告
No. In the obituaries.
这人我认识
I know this person.
Antonia Florentino 享年80岁
"Antonia Florentino, 80,
在梦里平静地离开了人世
Died peacefully in her sleep."
是自杀死的 对吧?
That's a suicide, right?
她是我的老保姆
She was my nanny.
你竟然还有老保姆?
You still have a nanny?
真幸运
Lucky.
小时候一直是她在照顾我
She took care of me most of my childhood.
我很爱她
I loved her so much.
节哀
So sorry.
我感同身受
That's kind of how I felt
就像我的老邻居Carla
about my old neighbor, Carla.
我是说 她虽然没照顾过我
I mean, she didn't take care of me,
但我小时候 她经常让我
But when I was a kid, she used to let me
用她的软管喝水
drink out of her hose.
最后一次我见Antonia 是她载着我
The last time I saw Antonia, she was driving me
以及冒牌的妮丽·费塔朵 去参加青少年选择奖
And a sloppy Nelly Furtado to the teen choice awards.
哦 我们可以在工作的时间哭泣啊?
Oh, are we allowed to cry at work now?
我之前都是在车里哭的
Cause I only do it in my car.
Max 你知道我意识到什么吗
Max, you know what I just realized?
这是在我保姆死后
This is the first time I've been here
我第一次踏足这里
since my nanny died.
刚在墨西哥快餐店你说了这个话
You just said that at Chipotle.
10分钟后你又说了一遍
And then you said it again ten minutes later,
还是在墨西哥快餐店
Also at Chipotle.
给点同情心啊
Show some sensitivity.
我哭是因为我的保姆死了
I was crying because my nanny died.
而且我们还得在墨西哥快餐店吃早午饭
And also because our grief brunch was at Chipotle.
Caroline 你保姆去世了?
Caroline, your nanny passed?
真可怜 这孩子 真不幸
My sympathies, sweetheart. That's a shame.
但是一个黑人的葬礼是最隆重的
But there is nothing better than a black funeral.
84年参加完我爷爷的葬礼后 我一直醉到现在
I'm still hung over from my grandpa's in '84.
Earl 我的保姆是个白人
Earl, my nanny was white.
你保姆是个白人?
Your nanny was white?
孩子 你以前真有钱
Child, you were rich.
你见到Han了吗?
Have you seen Han?
明天葬礼在费城举办
The funeral's in Philadelphia tomorrow,
我要请一天的假
And I need the day off.
我之前好像看到他了
Well, I think I saw him earlier.
不过也有可能 我看到的是只猫
But then again, it might have been a cat.
我们两个都要请一天假
Hey, we both need the day off.
我要跟你一起去 在精神上支持你
I'm going with you for moral support
我要吃一回费城牛肉芝士三明治
slash my first cheesesteak / I want to ride
我还要像坐破碎球那样 去骑一次独立钟
the liberty bell like a wrecking ball.
我刚在这本科学杂志中读了一篇超疯狂的文章
I just read the craziest article in this popular science
是关于白矮星、黑洞和天王星的
about White Dwarfs, Black Holes, and Uranus.
哦 不 重新开始
Oh, no. Let me start over.
Han 我们明天要请假 我的保姆去世了
Han, we need tomorrow off. My nanny died.
她就像我的母亲一样
She was like a mother to me.
但她不是你妈妈
But she was not your mother.
还有餐馆明确规定了
And diner rules clearly state
家属去世方可请假
you can only take off for the death of a family member.
规定还说工作期间不允许喝水
Well, the rules also say no drinking on the job,
但...
But...
好 你去吧
Okay, yes, you can go.
因为在韩国文化里
Because in my culture, it's important
尊敬长者是很重要的
to honor the elderly.
22岁之前 我都是和一个97岁的老人
I shared a bunk bed with a 97-year-old
睡上下铺
till I was 22.
你是睡上面还是下面?
Were you on the top or bottom?
我一直在下面的
Oh, I was always the bottom.
哦 不 让我重新说一次
Oh, no. Let me start over.
哎 Caroline
Hey, Caroline.
我收到你保姆去世的信息了
I got your nanny death text.
出于尊重 我穿了黑色衣服
So I'm wearing black out of respect.
还有 我大姨妈也来了
And also, I got my period.
Sophie 谢谢你 这真好
Thanks, Sophie. That's lovely.
是吗? 你指哪件事?
It is? Which part?
你知道 那时候在波兰 我保姆去世了
You know, back in Poland when my nanny died,
我如此心碎 都不忍心把她吃下去了
I was so heartbroken, I could barely eat her.
你吃你死去的保姆?
You ate your dead nanny?
那啥 山羊就是山羊
Well, a goat's a goat.
无论你给它起啥名都没关系的
It doesn't matter what you name it.
那羊肉味道真的很好
It's still good goat meat.
好了 我要去我的御用座位了
All right, I'll be in my booth.
请给我一份金枪鱼三明治和三片痛经药片
I'm going to order a Tuna Melt and three Midol, please.
等等 我们怎么去那里?
Wait, how are we gonna get there?
Bebe有车 我们可以问问她
Oh, Bebe said she had a car, we can just ask her.
我不想跟她坐一辆车
I don't want to get in a car with her.
我甚至都不想跟她说话
I don't even want to get in a conversation with her.
我可以载你
I can drive you.
我们得在我妹妹那停一下
We just have to stop at my sister's
就在巴克士郡 拿个无标记的包裹
in Bucks County, pick up an unmarked package,
然后去康乃狄克州把东西丢下来
and swing by Connecticut to drop it off.
Oleg 你运送的包裹里有非法物品吗?
Oleg, is there anything illegal about this delivery?
没有 就是些鞋子...
No, it's just some shoes...
塞了些可卡因在里面
stuffed with cocaine.
这些鞋子都是用印度大麻做的
Also the shoes are made of hashish.
我现在打电话给Bebe
I'll call Bebe.
好吧 但我要坐后面
Okay, but I'm sitting in the back
因为我可不想这疯女人扑向我
cause I don't want the crazy to get on me.
Bebe 实在太感谢你了
Bebe, I can't thank you enough
载我们去参加葬礼
for driving us to the funeral.
现在才20码 你可以稍微开快一点
We're only going 20. You can go faster if you want.
是啊 我们刚才被一棵树给超过了
Yeah, we just got passed by a tree.
我很高兴你带上这只神经紧绷的可卡犬
And I'm especially thrilled your nervous cocker spaniel
加了油 弄得像无线热点一样 和我们上路
with gas and hot spots got to join us.
好吧 现在你又100码了
Okay, now you're going 100.
我们可以开得稍微慢一点的
We can go slower if you want.
抱歉 我的问题在于 我相当极端
Sorry. Extremes... That's my thing.
有一次 我在一天之内搬到东京
One time I moved to Tokyo for a day.
- Max 我又感觉很受伤了  - 我懂
- Max, it just hit me again.  - I know.
就像是她给这狗喂了西兰花
It's like she feeds him broccoli.
不是
No.
Antonia真的死了
That Antonia is really dead.
好消息是 根据狗叫声
Well, the good news is, according to yelp,
她去世的地方 距离著名的
she's dead about two blocks
费城牛肉芝士三明治 只有两个街区
from the famous Philly Cheesesteak place.
Max 尊重下死者
Max, show some respect.
好吧 我不认识她
Well, I didn't know her.
事实上 我认为她是一个会带我去吃
In fact, I only know her as the lady who brought me
费城牛肉芝士三明治的女人
and cheesesteaks together.
尽管我们许久未见 但是对于
Even though we've never met, it'll mean so much
Antonia的家人来说 我的出席很有意义
to Antonia's family that I came out of respect.
这对我的治疗师也很有意义
It'll mean so much to my therapist
因为我走出了我的安全区
that I left my safe zone
而且只带了一只狗上路
and only brought one of the dogs.
Max 你认为我在念悼词的时候
Max, do you think in addition to my eulogy,
要不要从我的童年日记里添加些内容进去
I should read something from my childhood Journal?
不要 但我知道你还是会那么做
I don't, but I think you're gonna do it anyway.
"1997年 圣诞节早上
"Christmas morning, 1997.
Antonia用一杯热巧克力 以及
Antonia woke me up with a cup of hot cocoa
我最爱的薄荷棒棒糖 叫醒了我
and my favorite peppermint stick.
然后我们一起打开了圣诞礼物"
And then we opened presents."
1997年的圣诞节早上
Christmas morning, 1997.
我朝我妈脸上泼了一杯冷水
I threw cold water on my mother's face.
新年到来... 她还冻在原地
New year's day... Still no movement.
噢
Oh.
这是我们的合影 我只有这一张了
This is the only picture I still have of us.
这是我们一起过的第一个万圣节
It was our first Halloween together.
那年我四岁
I was four.
瞧这件她亲手为我缝制的 万圣节鸡宝宝的服装
Look at that cute little baby chick costume she made me.
唧 唧
Peep, peep.
喔 真可爱
Aw, so cute.
开车
Car.
我从来没有什么万圣节服装
I never had a Halloween costume.
我以前就把头发乱糟糟的卷成一团
I used to put my hair in a messy bun
然后一瘸一拐的 挨家挨户敲门
and stumble from door-to-door,
装作是我妈
telling people I was my mother.
这个万圣节 我扮成了我的医生 Michael
This Halloween, I went as my doctor, Michael.
我的狗狗打扮成了他的恋人 Joseph
And I dressed up my buddy here
我们一起出动了
as his lover, Joseph.
结果迷路了
We lost.
Antonia总是在我身边...
Antonia was always there for me...
万圣节 圣诞节 复活节... 每个节日
Halloween, Christmas, Easter... Every holiday.
真的 每天
Really, every day.
对我来说 她就像妈妈一样
She was really like a mother to me.
那你亲妈在哪?
Where was your real mother?
嘿 这狗是什么品种啊?
Hey, what kind of dog is that?
除了"揭人伤疤"这品种
I mean, besides "sad"?
她妈妈出轨 然后被赶出家门了
Her mother had an affair, got pushed out.
这是她的死穴 别乱戳
That's her hot spot, so don't lick it.
没关系 Max你不用采取安全措施保护我
It's okay, Max, I don't need any protection.
你不用采取安全措施?
You don't need protection?
你怎么和我从前约会的每个男人一样?
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
嘿 Bebe 没错 我妈妈是背叛了我爸
Bebe, yes, my mother was unfaithful
所以她被赶出家门了
to my father, so she was sent away.
但还好我有Antonia照看我
But I had Antonia and she took care of me.
她就是我的家人
She was my family.
你一定过得很辛苦吧 世上只有妈妈好
That must have been hard. Everybody needs a mother.
我要没妈肯定会疯了
I'd be crazy without my mother.
我每次约会都是我妈开车送我去
She drives me to all my appointments.
但现在你在开车
But you drive.
对...
Yeah...
但是我本来不该开的
But I'm not supposed to.
我让Bebe一个人留在车上没事吧?
It's okay I asked Bebe to wait in the car, right?
我觉得她应该会好好的吧 车窗留了缝
I mean, she'll be okay. We cracked a window.
她还有一个狗盆和一个磨牙棒
Yeah, and she's got a bowl and a chew-toy.
来吧 我们签到吧
Come on, let's sign in.
Max 和她家人会面时 我要振作起来
Max, I have to keep it together when I meet the family.
我不能太情绪化
I can't be all emotional.
看 我的手在颤抖 不妙啊
Look, my hand's shaking. This is terrible.
怎么? 我刚才名字没签好
What? It was a terrible signature.
而且这一页只签了五个名字而已
And there were only five other names on the page.
不要了
Get rid of it.
"不要了?"
"get rid of it"?
我上过的每个男人都是这么说的
Who are you, every guy I've ever dated?
Caroline Channing 好了
"Caroline Channing."
给 Max
Here, Max.
噢 看
Oh, look.
这些花 以及这些 都相当好看
The flowers and everything are so beautiful.
完事
There you go.
你签的是"费城牛肉芝士三明治"?
You signed "Phil E. Cheesesteak"?
你让我不许再提起这个
You told me not to mention it anymore,
所以这是用来提醒自己的
so it's just a reminder.
喂 Max 待会儿会有很多人
Okay, Max, there are gonna be a lot of people
会前来和寒暄 所以一会儿你要耐心点
who will want my attention, so please be patient
陪在我身边 当我的支柱
and stand next to me for the occasional supportive lean.
如果有人开始痛哭流涕
And if someone starts to get too weepy,
马上把他们推开
push them out of the way.
因为我不能让这身衣服沾上眼泪
Because I can't get tears on this dress.
明早九点前我还得把这衣服退回给百货公司
It has to be back to Barneys by 9:00 a.m.
你来了
You're here.
我们开始了 Max
Here we go, Max.
我是在和他说话
I was talking to him.
当然了 今天对于我们所有人来说都很悲痛
Of course you were. It's a very sad day for us all.
这也太尴尬了
That was rough.
噢 Max 看
Oh. Max, look.
这就是Antonia
This is Antonia.
哇 她看起来真的很和蔼
Wow. She looks really nice.
确实
She was.
我不知道她是军人
I didn't know she was in the military.
难怪她能折叠出那种有型的被角
But it does explain those fabulous bed sheet corners.
等等 你不知道你的保姆曾是海军?
Wait, you didn't know your nanny was a marine?
太糟了 要是我 我就会说
That's too bad, 'cause I'd be all,
"嘿 你们这些小富二代们!
"yo, other little rich kid!
我保姆能把你们脖子掰断了"
My nanny can snap your neck."
啊 看 这是她的姐妹 Cecelia和Angela
Oh, look. There are her sisters, Cecelia and Angela,
这是她的侄子和外甥
and there are her nieces and nephews.
这上面却没有我
And there is not me anywhere.
我的照片肯定和其他贵宾的一起
You know, my picture must be in the coffin
被挂在棺材里
With the other V.I.P.S.
如果你是个贵宾 能叫人给咱们上杯酒吗
If you're a V.I.P., can we get some bottle service?
下午好 女士们
Good afternoon, ladies.
我叫Anthony 是Antonia的外甥
I'm Anthony, Antonia's nephew.
这是个悲痛的日子
It's sad day, huh?
的确
Yes, it is.
啊
Oh.
我想我稍微不那么悲痛了
Think I just got a little less sad.
噢! Anthony!
Oh! Anthony!
住手 我们是一家人
Stop. We're family.
我是Caroline Channing
I'm Caroline Channing.
管你是谁 反正你很性感
You're Caroline "hot," is all I know.
你们需要包钱的信封吗?
You ladies need cash envelopes
还是你们有了?
or you guys cool?
我总是要准备一个现金信封的
I always need a cash envelope.
不好意思 什么的信封?
I'm sorry, envelopes for what?
意大利传统 在哀悼完死者之后
Well, at Italian wakes, the mourners give the family
哀悼者要给死者家属一点钱
a donation after they view the deceased.
所以看一次就要收费一次?
So it's pay-per-view?
这笑话不错
That was a good one.
嘿 你们稍后想一起喝一杯吗?
Hey, you want to go get a pop later?
我们一会就要走的 好了 Anthony
We're leaving right after, but yes, Anthony.
谢谢 我们要一个信封
Thank you. We'll take an envelope.
好的
All right.
她就躺在那
The body's right through there.
直接过去 直接穿过去
Go right ahead. Right through.
Anthony 住手
Anthony, stop.
我真的很紧张
I'm really nervous.
我以前从没见过尸体
I've never seen a dead body before.
我见过太多了
I've seen a bunch.
其中一些尸体是我害的
A couple of them were my fault.
我没有现金
I don't have any cash.
- 你有钱吗?  - 我看看钱包
- Do you have any money?  - Let me check my wallet.
这是密保诺牌密封袋 不是山寨货哦
This is a real Ziploc, not one of those knock-offs.
确保把信封给封好
Make sure you seal the envelope,
让别人以为里面全是25美分
So people think it's all quarters.
Max 要到我们了
Max, we're next.
我很害怕 拉住我的手
I'm afraid. Hold my hand.
拉手? 我们是什么关系?
Hold hands? What are we?
是基督教徒们的第五次约会吗?
On a Christian mingle fifth date?
求你了 Max 我很紧张
Please, Max. I'm nervous.
天啊 谢谢你
Oh, god. Thank you.
没事 现在把我的手还给我
Okay. Now give it back.
想怎样? 刚才已是我交往过最长的恋情了
What? That was just my longest relationship.
还有 我需要把这些零钱放到信封里
Plus, I need it to put this change in the envelope.
噢 她看起来很安详
Oh, she looks so peaceful.
Antonia 是我 Caroline
Hi, Antonia. It's me, Caroline.
我该不该亲她一下? 家属就在那边看着呢
Should I kiss her? The family is right there watching.
我们前面那个女士亲了她
The lady before us kissed her.
亲吧
Go for it.
她看起来不会打你的
Doesn't look like she'd fight you.
好吧 数三下
Okay, on the count of three.
一 二...
One, two...
不行! Max 拉着我的手当我...
No! Max, hold my hand again while I...
我们干了什么?
What do we do?
等等 留在那吧! 我们终究还是要给他们的
Wait, leave it! We were giving it to them anyway.
不能全给啊 这可是买牛肉芝士三明治的钱
Not all of it. That's our cheesesteak money.
留着吧 别管了
Leave it. Come on.
我真的感到非常 非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry about that.
我太紧张了 你懂的
My nerves got the best of me. You understand.
我是Cecelia Antonia的...
I'm Cecelia, Antonia's...
妹妹 我知道
Sister. I know.
你们长得挺像的
I see the resemblance.
我是Caroline
I'm Caroline.
哪个Caroline?
Caroline who?
哦 Caroline Channing
Oh. Caroline Channing.
哪个Caroline Channing?
Caroline Channing who?
我知道你很难过 我明白的
You're having a hard time processing. Understandable.
今天对于我们大家来说都是沉痛的一天
It's been a very emotional day for us all.
这姑娘哪来的?
Who is this girl?
你 我在哪见过你
You, I feel like I've seen somewhere.
你是从罗契斯特市来的
Are you Ricky's girl
Ricky的女朋友吗?
from Rochester?
可以啊 有什么好处吗?
I could be. What's in it for me?
我小的时候Antonia照顾过我
Antonia used to take care of me when I was little.
哦 Antonia是你的保姆
Oh, Antonia was your baby-sitter.
你能来真好
Very nice of you to come.
哦 她不只是我的"保姆"
Well, she was hardly my "baby-sitter."
十年来她悉心照顾着我
She took care of me every day for ten years.
我是Caroline Caroline Channing
Caroline. Caroline Channing.
不好意思 但我不认识你 亲
I'm sorry, but I don't know who you are, sweetheart,
但你似乎竭力想要提示我
Though it seems to be what you're hammering me about.
如果你们不介意
If you'll excuse me,
我得来根烟
I need a cigarette.
然后还得把我姐姐身上
And then I got to remove
那些钢镚儿拿掉
some of those pennies off of my sister.
这是棺材 不是许愿池
It's a coffin, not a wishing well.
这场葬礼真让人沮丧
This funeral turned out to be very depressing.
没错
Well, yeah.
室内有尸体 确实很扫兴的
Dead body in the room, generally a buzz-kill.
除非是爱尔兰式守丧
Unless it's an Irish wake...
可以在棺材边上玩啤酒弹珠
then you're playing beer pong off the coffin.
不 我是说 这真是难以置信
No, I mean, how is it possible
她的家人怎么会不认识我?
that the family doesn't even know me?
难道Antonia从来没跟他们提起过我?
Did Antonia never even mention me?
我们要往好处想
Let's focus on the positive.
Anthony是真心喜欢你的屁股
Anthony really liked your ass.
我和Antonia有过回忆
I know what Antonia and I had.
我们之间美好的回忆
This is what we had.
唧 唧
Peep, peep.
这些都是满满的回忆
That's what we had.
确实很满
Well, that's a lot.
可是我想她的家人
But I guess no one in this family
却拒绝承认 而且很可惜啊
wants to admit that, and it's a shame too
我的悼词写得非常好
because I had a great eulogy.
真的吗?
You do?
是的
Yes. I do.
你想看看吗?
Would you like me to share it with you?
非常想看
I most certainly would.
不会吧 你想给一个
You are not seriously eulogy-bombing
老太太念悼词?
that old lady, are you?
是她想要看我的悼词
She asked me about my great eulogy.
她可能有一百岁了
She's a hundred.
也许她听成了你有很赞的泌尿科医师
She probably thought you said you had a great urologist.
你有笔吗?
Do you have a pen?
我要记一下她的医生的名字
I'm getting the name of her doctor.
不是 夫人 我说的不是"泌尿科医师"
No, ma'am, I didn't say, "urologist."
我说的是"悼词" 很赞的悼词
I said, "eulogy." a great eulogy.
你为什么要念悼词?
Why would you give the eulogy?
因为我是Caroline Channing
Because I'm Caroline Channing.
谁啊?
Who?
Caroline Channing啊
Caroline Channing.
Antonia曾是我的保姆
Antonia was my nanny.
我家以前很有钱
My family was rich,
但是我爸偷了大家的钱
but then my father robbed everyone,
然后我们就变成了过街老鼠
And we became the scourge of society,
虽然那周被梅尔·吉布森
overshadowed a little bit by Mel Gibson
痛打犹太人给抢了头条
hating the jews that same week.
但你们肯定记得 是吧?
Surely, you remember?
亲爱的 我连自己怎么来的都不记得了
Honey, I don't even remember how I got here.
难以置信
I can't believe this.
我一直以为虽然小时候
I constructed my entire "happy" childhood
我被妈妈无情的抛弃了
on the fact that even though my mom left
但我的童年是"快乐的"
and apparently didn't love me,
因为有Antonia爱我
Antonia did.
但现在我明白了
And now I get here and I realize
没有人爱我 照顾我只是一份工作
no one loved me, I was just a paycheck.
和她照顾别的孩子没什么两样
One of the many kids she baby-sat.
真不知道我为什么要来
I don't even know why I bothered to come.
我去下洗手间 然后就可以走了
I'm going to the restroom and then we can just leave.
不好意思 嗨
Excuse me. Hi.
我是Ricky的女朋友Max
Max, Ricky's girl.
我理解你现在很难过
I know this is a hard time for you,
但我朋友也很难过
but it's a hard time for my friend as well.
虽然你从来没听说过她
And even though you never heard of her,
但你可不可以去告诉她
I was wondering if you could just go over there,
你记得她
and say you just remembered her,
因为Antonia过去常常提起她?
and that Antonia talked about her all the time?
我知道这话和事实是完全相反的
I know it's a 180 on your original story and a lie,
我本想给你点报酬的
and I'd offer to pay you for your trouble,
但是我的养老金
but my 401k is laying in that box
全都撒在你姐姐身上了
on top of your sister.
听着 我之所以让你俩留下
Look, I only permitted you two to stay
是因为去年Joe叔叔从屋顶摔下来的时候
'cause your Ricky was so nice to Uncle Joe
你家Ricky没少帮忙
when he fell off the roof last year.
但现在 请离开吧
But now, you gotta go.
好的 我走
Okay. Be that way.
但你别再指望着Ricky
But don't expect Ricky to pick up
会接送Joe叔叔做渗析
Uncle Joe for dialysis.
Max 你在干吗?
Max, what are you doing?
她家人让我把这个挂上
The family asked me to put it up.
因为他们想起你了
They just remembered you.
哦 天啊
Oh, my god.
我真可悲 你还得把照片
I'm so pathetic, you have to put up
挂上去 以此来安慰我吗?
my picture to make me feel better?
确实如此
In a way, yes.
照片挂在这儿
It belongs up there.
大家都会想知道这个孩子是谁
Who wouldn't want to know that kid?
很高兴认识你 Antonia
Nice to meet you, Antonia.
请不要来找我们
Please don't haunt us.
我们走吧 然后去吃牛肉芝士三明治!
Now, let's hit the road and get some freaking cheesesteaks!
Max 把照片拿下来
Max, please take that down.
太丢脸了
It's so embarrassing.
这里没一个人认识我
Nobody here knows anything about me.
他们也不认识我呢 鸡宝宝
They didn't know me either, chicken.
嘿 你叫谁鸡宝宝啊?
Hey, who you callin' chicken?
她叫我 那是Antonia给我起的小名
Me. That was Antonia's nickname for me.
你知道我是谁?
You know who I am?
当然了
Of course I do.
Antonia的鸡宝宝 唧唧
Antonia's little chick, her peep.
她很爱你
She loved you.
她很开心能给你做那件万圣节服装
And she loved making you that costume.
她在厨房的桌子上摆满了亮片
Took the whole kitchen table up with all those sequins,
但她认为你应当穿得光彩照人
but she knew you deserved to sparkle.
她太喜欢你了 我都忍不住抱怨了
She loved you so much, I couldn't begin to complain.
不好意思 你是哪位?
I'm so sorry. What was your name?
我是Meg O'hara 她以前的室友
I'm Meg O'hara. I was her roommate.
也是她爱人
And lover.
我们共度了30载人生
We were together 30 years.
大兵!
The military!
我就知道 没错吧
I know, right? I mean, come on.
这是在坦克上我抱着她的合影
That's me with my arm around her on that tank.
而她的家人毫不知情
And the family still had no clue.
老牌拉拉... 真酷
Vintage lez... very cool.
Toni会希望我把这些交给你
I know Toni would have wanted you to have these.
哦 谢谢你能来 鸡宝宝
Oh, thanks for coming, chicken.
也许你是这世上唯一一个
You're probably the only person in the world
如我这般单纯地爱着她的人了
who loved her as purely as I did.
Max 来啊
Max, look.
这是圣诞节
Christmas.
这是我生日
And my birthday.
还有全美青少年选择奖
And the Teen Choice Awards.
请节哀顺便
I'm sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
请大家吃费城牛肉芝士三明治!
Philly cheesesteaks for everybody!
当你在一辆雪佛兰坐上两小时
And you really haven't lived
带着九份牛肉芝士三明治 车上还有只臭狗
until you've driven two hours in a Chevy
就明白以前的一切苦难都是浮云
with nine cheesesteaks and a gassy animal.
怎么? 我那份在车上吃了
What? I ate mine in the car.
嘿 Earl 你错过了一场葬礼
Hey, Earl, you missed one hell of a funeral.
你真应该来看看
You should have come.
那里有不少八九十岁的辣妹
There were some hot octogenarians,
我肯定被她们其中一位的"老人热"
and I got a definite "jungle fever" vibe
给感染了
from one of them.
姑娘 像我这种年纪的人
Girl, at my age, you don't go
会离葬礼远远的
anywhere near funerals.
要是一不留神被埋进墓穴里
You accidentally doze off, you spend six hours
还得用六小时的时间爬出来呢
digging yourself out of the ground.
嘿 你怎么样啊 鸡宝宝?
Hey, how you holding up, chicken?
我很好 谢谢
I'm okay. Thanks.
Max 要是有一天我死了
And Max, when I die,
别人去不去我的葬礼我都不在乎
I don't care who else is at my funeral,
只要你在那儿
as long as you're there.
我当然会在场
Of course I'll be there.
凶手一般都会出现 以摆脱自己的嫌疑
The murderer always shows up to throw off the cops.
还有 别浪费钱买骨灰盒
Also, save the money on a casket
只要让我穿着迪奥套装 画着烟熏妆就可以了
and just toss me in a hole wearing Dior and a smoky eye.
如果我太胖... 那就把我火化了
Unless I'm fat... then burn me.
我不想要葬礼
Well, I don't want a funeral.
要是我死了 把尸体放在大炮里
When I die, just shove my corpse into a cannon
把我发射到特朗普赌场就好了
and blow me directly into the Trump Casino.